<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ironSource on Daniel Berstein</title><link>/categories/ironsource/</link><description>Recent content in ironSource on Daniel Berstein</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/ironsource/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recommendation :: Alon Ohad</title><link>/recommendation/2016/alon-ohad/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate><author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author><guid>/recommendation/2016/alon-ohad/</guid><description>&lt;p>I know Daniel from our mutual work at IronSource. Daniel, was a valuable asset in our department. He
is extremely knowledgeable on range of handy technologies. He knows his way in Linux very well and
also PHP, and other web, server side stuff. But more than everything, he is always willing to help his team
members as much as he can. He devote himself to every task as much as he can and I feel privileged working
with him.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Recommendation :: Eran Hurvits</title><link>/recommendation/2016/eran-hurvits/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate><author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author><guid>/recommendation/2016/eran-hurvits/</guid><description>&lt;p>Daniel is a great developer! He worked with me for 2 years, and in the past year we worked on several
projects together. Daniel designed and developed many of our operational systems, and created high
quality systems that improved the business significantly, and supported that operational activity. He is Very
responsible, target oriented, creative and into the details, and it was It was a pleasure working with him!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Recommendation :: Tal Kdoshim</title><link>/recommendation/2016/tal-kdoshim/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate><author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author><guid>/recommendation/2016/tal-kdoshim/</guid><description>&lt;p>It was a true pleasure working with Daniel for the past 2 years. Daniel is very thorough, creative and highly
devoted to his work. Daniel is a great team player and a full partner for achieving business goals quickly and
thoroughly.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>