<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>manager on Daniel Berstein</title>
        <link>/tags/manager/</link>
        <description>Recent content in manager on Daniel Berstein</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="/tags/manager/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        
        <item>
            <title>Recommendation :: Alejandro Jara Miranda</title>
            <link>/recommendation/2001/alejandro-jara-miranda/index.html</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate>
            <author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author>
            <guid>/recommendation/2001/alejandro-jara-miranda/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Daniel es una de esas personas que uno agradece haber tenido como compañero. Con buena disposición
a trabajar en equipo, y siempre dispuesto a compartir su conocimiento; aprendí de él que si una solución
aparentemente no es posible, se puede inventar. Y que si estás absolutamente convencido de algo, todavía
debes preguntarte si tienes razón. Cómo lo recuerdo: creativo y místico.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Recommendation :: Amit Roseberger</title>
            <link>/recommendation/2008/amit-roseberger/index.html</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate>
            <author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author>
            <guid>/recommendation/2008/amit-roseberger/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;I worked with Daniel for almost two years while he was leading the development of the Zend Web site.
Daniel is super responsive, quick to handle requests and has a good eye for details. Many times, Daniel fixed
last minuet issues that were found during our release process and by that helped me role out our products on
time. Amit Roseberger Zend Core Group Leader. Zend Technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Recommendation :: Boaz Ziniman</title>
            <link>/recommendation/2008/boaz-ziniman/index.html</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate>
            <author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author>
            <guid>/recommendation/2008/boaz-ziniman/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;I had the pleasure to work and manage one of the brightest developers (PHP in my case) I have ever meet,
with the most unique approach to software architect, design and coding. Daniel is constantly looking for
new solutions and doesn&amp;rsquo;t afraid to dive into new, unfamiliar challenges, something I always appreciate in a
software developer. Working and managing Daniel was a unique experience and I hope we will have a chance
to work together again in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Recommendation :: Daniel Kushner</title>
            <link>/recommendation/2008/daniel-kushner/index.html</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate>
            <author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author>
            <guid>/recommendation/2008/daniel-kushner/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Daniel is a professional, passionate, and dedicated asset to Zend Technologies. He enjoys his work and
provides superb internal-customer satisfaction. It has been a pleasure having Daniel as a part of my team.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Recommendation :: Humberto Pröschle</title>
            <link>/recommendation/2004/humberto-pr%C3%B6schle/index.html</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate>
            <author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author>
            <guid>/recommendation/2004/humberto-pr%C3%B6schle/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;I recommend Daniel, and especially applaud his ability to work on high technology projects&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Recommendation :: Jacob Shwirtz</title>
            <link>/recommendation/2005/jacob-shwirtz/index.html</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate>
            <author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author>
            <guid>/recommendation/2005/jacob-shwirtz/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Daniel was an absolute pleasure to work with. He was always able to bring a great big-picture perspective
to our projects and do much more than just what he was hired for. Many projects wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have succeeded
without his attention to detail and ability to manage resources most effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Recommendation :: Oleg Sverdlov</title>
            <link>/recommendation/2011/oleg-sverdlov/index.html</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate>
            <author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author>
            <guid>/recommendation/2011/oleg-sverdlov/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;As a software engineer, Daniel provides industrial-grade solutions in time and according to specs. He works
in a team as well as an one-man special task force, always bringing out high quality work. As a system
architect, he&amp;rsquo;s an independent and creative thinker. As a skilled craftsman, Daniel is able to come up with
creative solutions that often exceed expectations. Daniel&amp;rsquo;s friendly and ongoing personality makes it simple to
work with him even for multicultural teams. It is a pleasure to work together with him.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Recommendation :: Sergiy Pechonkin</title>
            <link>/recommendation/2012/sergiy-pechonkin/index.html</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate>
            <author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author>
            <guid>/recommendation/2012/sergiy-pechonkin/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;I worked with Daniel in the Development Department at Afterdownload. He is very goal oriented and
an exceptional team player, very devoted to his work and always wants to do everything in a perfect way.
Daniel is one of the best programmers I worked with. There were several situations when under extreme
pressure Daniel suggested brilliant solutions to the problems we had. Daniel is always ready to help other
team members. I really enjoyed working together with Daniel.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Recommendation :: Yoram Elalouf</title>
            <link>/recommendation/2008/yoram-elalouf/index.html</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate>
            <author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author>
            <guid>/recommendation/2008/yoram-elalouf/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;As the Director of Global Services at Zend I have numerous interactions with Daniel,I wanted to express my
deep appreciation and satisfaction from Daniel&amp;rsquo;s work.His help is priceless, his responsiveness is great, his
professionalism is very high and in addition he is fun to work with. I highly recommend him as a person and
an employee.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>