<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>product manager on Daniel Berstein</title><link>/tags/product-manager/</link><description>Recent content in product manager on Daniel Berstein</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/product-manager/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recommendation :: Aviv Katz</title><link>/recommendation/2008/aviv-katz/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate><author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author><guid>/recommendation/2008/aviv-katz/</guid><description>&lt;p>Daniel is a great software developer and a great team player His knowledge and willingness to help others
made him a company wide resource for questions. It was a great pleasure working with Daniel, hope to work
with him also in the future.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Recommendation :: Eran Hurvits</title><link>/recommendation/2016/eran-hurvits/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate><author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author><guid>/recommendation/2016/eran-hurvits/</guid><description>&lt;p>Daniel is a great developer! He worked with me for 2 years, and in the past year we worked on several
projects together. Daniel designed and developed many of our operational systems, and created high
quality systems that improved the business significantly, and supported that operational activity. He is Very
responsible, target oriented, creative and into the details, and it was It was a pleasure working with him!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Recommendation :: Tal Kdoshim</title><link>/recommendation/2016/tal-kdoshim/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate><author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author><guid>/recommendation/2016/tal-kdoshim/</guid><description>&lt;p>It was a true pleasure working with Daniel for the past 2 years. Daniel is very thorough, creative and highly
devoted to his work. Daniel is a great team player and a full partner for achieving business goals quickly and
thoroughly.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Recommendation :: Yossi Leon</title><link>/recommendation/2008/yossi-leon/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 08:22:22 +0200</pubDate><author>Daniel Berstein (daniel@basegeo.com)</author><guid>/recommendation/2008/yossi-leon/</guid><description>&lt;p>Daniel is a responsible and dedicated engineer who put a lot of effort in bringing the company&amp;rsquo;s site and
infrastructure to high level standards. Daniel and I worked close together when it has to do with launching
new products. Daniel impressed me with his professional skills and helped me as Product manager to achieve
my product&amp;rsquo;s goals. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that Daniel will succeed in any company he will work for and i wish him good
luck.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>